Inventory of the Records of Joseph Dupuy Eggleston 1913-1919
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series II 1912-1919
  - Hatcher, Watkins ("Inky") 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-423)
  - Inventories, Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5-424)
    Department of Civil Engineering; Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; Office of the Registrar; Office of D.O. Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Heat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, Campus, Steam Laundry; Dining Hall Department; and Farm Department
  - H--miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-425)
    Buckeye Coal and Coke Company
  - Howard Hubble 1918 (Box-folder 5-426)
    Notable letterhead from Robert E. Lee Hall of the Blue Ridge Association; and YMCA
  - Holstein--Friesians Records 1918 (Box-folder 5-427)
  - Holden, R.J.; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Geology (Box-folder 5-428)
  - Leroy Hodges 1918 (Box-folder 5-429)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor's Office; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Treasurer; and Coal contract information
  - J.N. Hillman, Commonwealth of Virginia, State Board of Education 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-430)
  - Hill, H.H. 1918 (Box-folder 5-431)
    VPI General Alumni Association
  - Henderson W.F. 1918 (Box-folder 5-432)
  - Hazing--Fox (VPI) 1919 (Box-folder 5-433)
    Office of the Commandant; Office of the Registrar; Office of the Dean of the General Faculty; Department of Geology; and Department of Modern Languages
  - W.E. Hathaway 1918 (Box-folder 5-434)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Game and Inland Fisheries
  - J.L. Hart 1918 (Box-folder 5-435)
    Farmville Herald; and J.D. Eggleston editorials
  - Lucius Gregory 1918 (Box-folder 5-436)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Chase City Manufacturing Company
  - Carter Glass 1918 (Box-folder 5-437)
  - G.H. Gibboney 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-438)
    Includes notable letterhead from Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Scholarships
  - G-Miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-439)
    Includes notable letterhead from Merchants' and Farmers' Bank
  - F--miscellaneous 1917-1919 (Box-folder 5-440)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Farm Journal and notable letterhead from the Prang Company
  - J.B. Fogleman 1918 (Box-folder 5-441)
    Notable letterhead from Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station
  - J.G. Ferneyhough 1918 (Box-folder 5-442)
    Virginia State Livestock Sanitary Board, State Veterinary Department; and permit for medicinal whiskey
  - Henry D. Flood 1918 (Box-folder 5-443)
  - S.L. Ferguson 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-444)
    Agricultural high schools
  - E--miscellaneous 1918 (Box-folder 5-445)
    YMCA--sex education
  - Extension Division Reports 1918-1921 (Box-folder 5-446)
  - G.W. Everett 1918 (Box-folder 5-447)
  - F.W. Ehart 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-448)
    Includes letterhead from Town of Blacksburg; Septic tank
  - D--miscellaneous 1918 (Box-folder 5-449)
    Includes notable letterhead from the John C. Winston Company; views of women in agriculture
- Series III
  - Castle and Wilson 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-450)
    Powerhouse boilers
  - Cate, W.B. 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-451)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Florida Normal Institute and Commercial College
  - Chapman, H. Powell 1918 (Box-folder 5-452)
  - Cholera Serum (Box-folder 6-453)
  - Claxton, Dr. P.P. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-454)
    Department of Interior, Department of Education
  - Clement, N.E. 1918 (Box-folder 6-455)
  - Cook, J.W. 1918 (Box-folder 5-456)
    Includes notable letterhead from Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Coal Delivery
  - Cutherell, Milton 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-457)
    Purchasing
  - C--miscellaneous 1917-1919 (Box-folder 6-458)
    The Royal Society of Literature; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; State Board of education, Department of Public Instruction; and Southern Railway System
  - Dr. Charles W. Dabney 1918 (Box-folder 6-459)
  - Dancing 1919 (Box-folder 6-460)
  - Jackson Davis 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-461)
    Agricultural High School for Coloreds; Notable letterhead from Murphy's Hotel
  - Governor of the Commonwealth of Virginia--Davis 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-462)
    Workers' Compensation Act; Hazing; Appropriations from General Assembly; Coal
  - R.E. Denny 1918 (Box-folder 6-463)
  - John C. Dilton, Assistant Fuel Administrator for Virginia 1918
    Coal; United States Fuel Administration
  - Drinkard, A.W. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-465)
    Salary increases for employees at Virginia agricultural Experiment Station; Annual Report--Experiments Performed
  - Du Pont Company 1918 (Box-folder 6-466)
  - W.E. Barlow, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of metallurgy and Metallography 1918 (Box-folder 6-467)
  - Board of Visitors 1918 (Box-folder 6-468)
    Appropriations, Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor's Office
  - G.B. Bright 1917 (Box-folder 6-469)
  - W.H. Burruss 1916-1917 (Box-folder 6-470)
  - T.p. Campbell--Dean of the Faculty (Box-folder 6-471)
    Electric lighting; act to promote vocational education
  - C.C. Carson--Commandant 1917 (Box-folder 6-472)
  - d.M. Clayd regarding Extension position 1916 (Box-folder 6-473)
  - M. Cutherell 1917 (Box-folder 6-474)
  - Department Heads, Virginia Polytechnic Institue--Expenses for Departments 1917 (Box-folder 6-475)
    Sjops Department; Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; Summer School; Department of Metallurgy and Metallography; and Department of Chemistry and Chemical Engineering
  - A.W. Drinkard 1917 (Box-folder 6-476)
    Requests for appropriations for Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; College for colored youths
  - Extesion Work Historical Statement 1916 (Box-folder 6-477)
  - Faculty Matters, Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1915-1917 (Box-folder 6-478)
    Department of Geology; Shops Department; Student fines; Examination schedule; Classroom time; and moving picture apparatus
  - Field House (Student's Resolution) 1914-1915, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 6-479)
    Includes notable letterhead from Virginia Polytechnic Institute Atheletic Association; Office of D.O. Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Hat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, Campus, Steam Laundry; Office of the Treasurer; Department of Modern Languages; Heating the library
  - F.D. Fromme, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1917 (Box-folder 6-480)
  - G--miscellaneous 1917 (Box-folder 6-481)
    Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute
  - Dr. W.F. Henderson 1917 (Box-folder 6-482)
  - H.H. Hill, Executive Secretary, General Alumni Association 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-483)
    Institution's progress along military lines; Major Lloyd W. Williams; Alumnigram
  - C.W. Holdaway, Associate Dairy Husbandman 6-484 (Box-folder 6-484)
    Creamery matters
  - Hon. Herbert Hoover 1917 (Box-folder 6-485)
    Includes notable letterhead from Herbert Hoover, Washington D.C.; church participation in food conservation
  - D.F. Honston--Secretary of Agriculture 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-486)
    Memorandum regarding importation of nursery stock into the United States
  - J.R. Hutcheson 1917-1919 (Box-folder 6-487)
    district extension agents in agricultural and home economics
  - T.B. Hutcheson 1917 (Box-folder 6-488)
    Water rent; Coal mine
  - Jesse M. Jones 1916 (Box-folder 6-489)
    Includes notable letterhead from Cedarville Stock Farm; women extension agent controversy--Miss Scott affair
  - Jesse M. Jones (Part 2) 1917-1919 (Box-folder 6-490)
    Cooperatice extension work; notable letterhead from Hotel Harrington; Negro farmers; notable letterhead from Negro Teachers' Association
  - Dr. Bradford Knapp 1916-1917 (Box-folder 6-491)
    Miss Scott affair
  - Dabney S. Lancaster 1917 (Box-folder 6-492)
  - Claudius Lee (Box-folder 6-493)
    Program clock
  - Legislature Bond Issue and Annuity 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-494)
    Includes notable letterhead from Alleghany Ore and iron company; notable letterhead from Miller, Rhoads, and Swartz Dry Goods, Inc.; notable letterhead from Norfolk and Western Railway Company; notable letterhead from Sydnor Pump and Well Company; and notable letterhead from Virginia Livestock Sanitary Board, State Veterinary Department
  - Legislature 1918 (Box-folder 6-495)
    Proposed annuity increases; notable letterhead from Alleghany Ore and Iron Company; notable letterhead from Miller, Rhoads, and Swartz Dry Goods, Inc.; notable letterhead from Shenandoah Life Insurance Company; Shops Department, Virginia Polytechnic Institute; and notable letterhead from Commonwealth of Virginia, Senate Chamber
  - E.A. Long--Principal, Christiansburg Institute (Box-folder 6-496)
    Christiansburg Hospital; correspondence regarding volume of autograph letters
  - L--miscellaneous 1916 (Box-folder 6-497)
  - Chas. G. Maphis 1918 (Box-folder 6-498)
    Association of Virginia Colleges; Smith-Hughes Act
  - Thomas S. Martin--Senator 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-499)
    United States Senate Committee on Appropriations; Fuel--coal, coal mine
  - O.B. Martin 1916-1917 (Box-folder 6-500)
    Women Extension agents in Virginia; Miss Scott Affair; Girls' club and home demonstration work
  - D.O. Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Heat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, camous, Steam Laundry 1915-1917 (Box-folder 6-501)
    Office of the Dean of Faculty; Department fo Mechanical Engineering; Requests for repairs and renovations; Electric lighting
  - C.P. Miles, Virginia Polytechnic Institute Athletic Association 1917 (Box-folder 6-502)
    Field House
  - J.h. mongomery--Executive Secretary--The Co-operative Education Society 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-503)
  - Mrs. B.B. Munford (Mary C.B. Munford), [President, Co-operative Education Association] 1914-1919 (Box-folder 6-504)
    Correspondence regarding the use of Mumford's Virginia's Attitude Toward Slavery and Secession in the schools; The Co-operative Education Association of Virginia Admission of women to the university
  - M--miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-505)
    Correspondence from Robert Moton, principal, Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute regarding disposition of German African colonies; Training of colored young men and women
  - N--miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-506)
  - J.J. Owens--Steward of Dining Halls 1917 (Box-folder 6-507)
    Dining hall rates
  - O--miscellaneous 1918 (Box-folder 6-508)
  - J.R. Parrott 1917 (Box-folder 6-509)
    Shops Department of the Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Power plant; Parrott's shop duties controversy; Price increases for faculty
  - W.M. Perry 1916-1918 (Box-folder 6-510)
    Four issues of Boys' Club letter
  - E.R. Price 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-511)
    Hazing incident--John Fox; VPI in war time
  - H.L. Price, Horticulturalist, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1917 (Box-folder 6-512)
  - Priddy, Lawrence 1913 (Box-folder 6-513)
    Includes notable letterhead from Lawrence Priddy Insurance; financing new college shops
  - S.R. Pritchard as Chairman of Faculty Atheletic Committee 1917 (Box-folder 6-514)
  - P--miscellaneous 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-515)
    Includes notable letterhead from Pocahantas Coal Sales Company Coal
  - L.S. Randolph 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-516)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Mechanical Engineering; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Applied Mechanics and Experimental Engineering; Heating; Plunkett coal mines; Water supply; Coal consumption; Vocational Education
  - F.L. Robeson 1917 (Box-folder 6-517)
    Letter regarding Stockton Heath shot in Professor Vawter's home
  - R--miscellaneous 1919 (Box-folder 6-518)
  - T.O. Sandy 1916-1918 (Box-folder 6-519)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Grove Stock Farm; notable letterhead from Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute; Cooperative extension work in agriculture and home economics
  - Wm. D. Sanders 1917 (Box-folder 6-520)
    Virginia Agrilcultural Experitment Station; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Employment Bureau; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the President; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Veterinary Science; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor's Office
  - J.H. Schultz--Steward of Dining Halls 1917 (Box-folder 6-521)
    Cost of dining hall suppies
  - Chas. W. Sumpter 1916 (Box-folder 6-522)
    Cheese industry at Spring Valley (Grayson County); treatment for "Black Head" diease in turkeys; local fruit culture
  - Claude A. Swanson (U.S. Senator) 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-523)
  - S--Miscellaneous 1918 (Box-folder 6-524)
    Letterhead from Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Notable letterhead from War Camp Community Services; Commonwealth of Virginia, Office of the Attorney General; Coal
  - Tyler, J. Hoge 1918 (Box-folder 6-525)
  - Western Union 1916-1918 (Box-folder 6-526)
    Telegraph Service
  - N.O. Wood C+P Telephone Company 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-527)
    Telephone Service
  - J.E. Williams 1917 (Box-folder 6-528)
  - Authur D. Wright (supervisor of colored Schools--VA) 1918 (Box-folder 6-529)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, State Board of Education; Agricultural high schools for Negroes; Proposed school in Blacksburg; Rosenwald Fund for rural schools for colored children; Smith-Hughes Act
  - W--miscellaneous 19181-1919 (Box-folder 6-530)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, House of Delegates; Commonwealth of Virginia, Secretary of the Commonwealth; Office of the State Commissioner of Prohibition; Georgia Land and Livestock Company
  - Emma S. Yerby 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6-531)
  - Agnew, Ella 1914-1918 (Box-folder 6-532)
    United States Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry; State agent for home demonstration work; Smith-Lever fund; Miss Scott affair
  - Agnew, Ella G.--Field Reports 194-1915 (Box-folder 6-533)
  - Annual Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 6-534)
  - Atkinson, Sally J. 1915 (Box-folder 6-535)
    Correspondence regarding women's share in Smith-Lever appropriations
  - Batten, Mittie--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 6-536)
  - Burke, Belle R.--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 6-537)
  - Hagy, Claudia M. (Miss)--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-538)
  - Hardy, Mary B.--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-539)
  - Herman, Bertha--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-540)
  - Hodsden, Bessie M.--Field Reports 1915 (Box-folder 7-541)
  - Hudson, Lessie--Field Reports 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-542)
  - Hughes, Hallie G.--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-543)
  - H--Miscellaneous 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-544)
  - Jayne, Beulah M.--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-545)
  - Jenkins, L.A. (Miss)--Field Reports 7-546
  - Jerrall, Josephine--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-547)
  - Johnson, Emily J.--Field Reports 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-548)
  - King, Margaret (Mrs.)--Field Reports 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-549)
  - K--miscellaneous 1915 (Box-folder 7-550)
  - McFarland, Mazie (Miss)--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-551)
  - Madison, Suzie D.--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-552)
  - Manning, E.M. (Miss)--Field Reports 1915 (Box-folder 7-553)
  - Micon, Frances R.--Field Reports 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-554)
  - Mortan, Nellie K.--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-555)
  - M--Miscellaneous 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-556)
  - Phillips, Avie E.--Field Reports 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-557)
  - P--miscellaneous 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-558)
  - R--miscellaneous 1915 (Box-folder 7-559)
  - St. Clair, Mary M.--Field Reports 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-560)
  - Sale, Annie E.--Field Reports 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-561)
  - Slocum, Slyvia H.--Field Reports 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-562)
  - Stebbins--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-563)
  - Stinson, Lorn--Field Reports 1914-1916 (Box-folder 7-564)
  - S-miscellaneous 1912-1916 (Box-folder 7-565)
  - Rhea Clarke Scott, Assistant State Agent, Home Demonstration Work 1912-1916 (Box-folder 7-565a)
    Women's clubs; Report of the Demonstration Plot at the State Normal School for 1915, Harrisonburg, Virginia
  - T--miscellaneous 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-566)
  - Wallace, Johnnie F. (Mrs.)--Field Reports 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-567)
  - Wills, Virginia D.--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-568)
  - Woolfolk, Kate--Field Reports 1914 (Box-folder 7-569)
  - Eggleston 1913-1915, 1918 (Box-folder 7-570)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Game and Inland Fisheries; Virginia State Livestock Sanitary Board, State Veterinary Department
  - German Club 1913 (Box-folder 7-571)
  - Trucks 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-572)
    Includes notable letterhead from Buick; notable letterhead from Federal Motor Truck Company
  - Smith-Lever Salary Voucher 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-573)
  - Admission Requirements, Including Residency 1915 (Box-folder 7-574)
  - Agriculture 1916 (Box-folder 7-574)
  - Agriculture 1916 (Box-folder 7-575)
  - Alumni 1915, 1917, 1919 (Box-folder 7-576)
  - Appropriations 1917 (Box-folder 7-577)
  - Athletic Association 1900, 1914-1915, 1917 (Box-folder 7-578)
    Question of professional players on football team; controversy over "Bumps" Turner, professional wrestler, on the football team; Letter from the Office of the Commandant regarding fire hazards in the Student Pressing Club
  - VPI-VMI 1919 (Box-folder 7-579)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Register; Annual Thanksgiving football game
  - Band 1917-1918 (Box-folder 7-580)
    Correspondence from Department of State, Washington regarding detention of VPI instructor in Italy for military service; Request for salary of V.P.I. Cadet Band for 1918-1919
  - Blacksburg 1913-1918 (Box-folder 7-581)
    Includes notable letterhead from J. Hoge Woolwine regarding V.P.I. competitition with the merchants of Blacksburg; Anna Campbell, teacher; Correspondence from G.R. Ragan, architect regarding plan for Blacksburg Public School; Town use of water; Letter from D.H. Keister, Mayor of Blacksburg regarding Main Street, delivery carts, and other town matters
  - Board of Trade, Blacksburg 1915 (Box-folder 7-582)
  - Ed Black--petition regarding land for high school 1913-1914 (Box-folder 8-583)
  - Board of Visitors 1913-1914 (Box-folder 7-584)
  - Commandant 1914-1918 (Box-folder 7-585)
  - Corps of Cadets 1913, 1915, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-586)
    Notepaper from Hotel Roanoke; Correspondence from american League to Limit Armaments; Hazing incident
  - Thompson, W.O.--ROTC 1916-1917 (Box-folder 7-587)
    Association of American Agricultural Colleges and Experiment Stations
  - Crop Pest Commission 1913-1914 (Box-folder 6-588)
  - Discipline 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6-589)
    Includes notable letterhead from Hunt Club Shoes
  - Eggleston, J.D.--Personal 1915-1919 (Box-folder 7-590)
    Letter to J.E. Williams regarding Eggleston's accomplistments during his administration; notable letterhead from the Executive Committee of Publication of the Presbyterian Church in the united States, Editorial Department; Correspondence from Christiansburg Industiral institute regarding Dr. Eggleston's election to Board of Directors of Christiansburg Colored Hospital; notable letterhead from City of Asheville, North Caroline; and South Carolina Cotton Association
  - Employee Relations 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-591)
    Correspondence from Commonwealth of Virginia, Bureau of Labor and Industrial Statistics, Commssioner's Office regarding work hours of women employed in the laundry; notable letterhead from the National Automatic Sprinkler Association
  - Evolution of the College 1913, 1915 (Box-folder 7-592)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Southern Planter; Collegiate Training in Agriculture at VPI
  - Expenses 1916 (Box-folder 7-593)
    Student expenses; Tabulated Comparartive Lists of College Fees etc., 1891-1916
  - Extension Work 1914, 1916 (Box-folder 7-594)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Farmer Boy
  - Faculty and Staff (Box-folder 7-595)
    Staff and Officers from 1872 to July 1, 1919
  - Fraternities 1915-1916 (Box-folder 7-596)
    Letter from Eggleston regarding requiremtnet to sign pledge before signing for matricultaion and order of the Board of Visitors disbanding fraternities; pernission to organize Delta Sigma Sigma fraternity
  - Fraternities 1916 (Box-folder 7-597)
    Letter from R.H. Price, member of the Public School Board, Blacksburg District, regarding fraternities
  - Hazing 1914-1915, 1919 (Box-folder 7-598)
  - Honorary Degrees 1918 (Box-folder 7-599)
  - Insurance 1915, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-600)
  - Jewish Holidays 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-601)
    Includes letterhead from Herman Hecht, Baker of Fine Breads and Cakes
  - Library 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-602)
  - Literary Societies 1917 (Box-folder 7-603)
    Correspondence from The Bugle
  - Media Relations 1913-1917 (Box-folder 7-604)
    Includes letterhead from the Richmond Virginia
  - Price, E.R. (public relations) 1913-1915 (Box-folder 7-605)
  - Schubert, E.A. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7-606)
    Norfolk and Western Railway company public relations
  - Public Relations--E.R. Price 1916 (Box-folder 7-607)
  - Milton (Box-folder 7-608)
  - Winston, J.R. 1918 (Box-folder 7-609)
    Name of the college
  - NCAA 1917 (Box-folder 7-610)
  - Negro 1918 (Box-folder 7-611)
    Induction in the military
  - Physical Plant 1911, 1915, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 7-612)
    Includes notable letterhead from Pyrene Manufacturing Company; William L. Pierce insurance statement; Hauling crushed stone on the Norfolk and Western Railway; and Proposal for steam heating aparatus.
  - Prohibition 1915-1917 (Box-folder 7-613)
  - Cannon, James, Superintendant, Anti-Saloon League of Virginia--Prohibition 1917 (Box-folder 7-614)
  - Rhodes Scholars 1919 (Box-folder 7-615)
  - Roads 1916, 1918 (Box-folder 7-616)
  - Smithfield 1919 (Box-folder 7-617)
  - Smith-Hughes Act 1918 (Box-folder 7-618)
  - Southern Railway Company 1915 (Box-folder 7-619)
  - Swanson, Sen. Claude (Box-folder 7-620)
  - Telephone and Telegraph 1915, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-621)
  - Trials and Tribulations 1915, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7-622)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Hotel Carroll; pasteurization of milk
  - Trinkle, E.Lee 7-623 (Box-folder 7-623)
  - Tyler, J. Hoge 1915 (Box-folder 7-624)
  - VPI 1919 (Box-folder 7-625)
  - Water Problems 1913 (Box-folder 7-626)
    Analyses of the college and town springs
  - Women 1913-1914, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 7-627)
    Includes correspondence from Aubrey E. Strode, 19th Senatorial District (Amherst) Commonwealth of Virginia, Senate Chamber; notable letterhead from Equal sufferage League of Virginia; notable letterhead from Stonewall Jackson College (for Women), Abington
  - Yellow Sulphur Springs 1918 (Box-folder 7-628)
  - YMCA (Box-folder 7-629)
    National war Work council of the Young Men's Christian Associations of the united States, Department of the East; Negro work in Virginia; correspondence from Paul N. Derring, General Secretary; Annual Report of the Student Department of the State Young men's Christian Association, April 1, 1917-April 1, 1918
  - Miscellaneous 1914 (Box-folder 7-630)
  - Carneal and Johnson, Architects and Consulting Engineers 1915-1919 (Box-folder 7-631)